(Sheldon:)Tomorrow.
(Sheldon:)Yes, I'll pay.
All right, goodbye.
All right.
(Sheldon:)Time to learn rock climbing.
(Sheldon:)You know, I am a fan of ventriloquism.
(Sheldon:)Maybe you, me and your dummy
could go get a hot beverage.
(Sheldon:)He could talk while you drink.
Nope. I wanna climb some rocks.
(Sheldon:)This appears significantly more monolithic
than it did on my laptop.
You know, one expects to see hominids
learning to use bones as weapons.
- Hey, you afraid of heights, Cooper?
- Hardly.
A fear of heights is illogical.
(Sheldon:)Fear of falling, on the other hand,
is prudent and evolutionary.
(Sheldon:)What would you say
is the minimum altitude...
(Sheldon:)...I need to achieve to cement
our newfound friendship?